<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>CloudBees Jenkins Support on Customer Success Onboarding</title>
    <link>https://example.com/support/</link>
    <description>Recent content in CloudBees Jenkins Support on Customer Success Onboarding</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 10 Dec 2019 18:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://example.com/support/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>CloudBees Jenkins Support Offering and Scope</title>
      <link>https://example.com/support/offeringandscope/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Oct 2017 15:26:15 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://example.com/support/offeringandscope/</guid>
      <description>Enterprise-class, global support and the collected wisdom of CloudBees engineers and expert Jenkins users. Learn more about the behavior of your Jenkins installation and greatly simplify your learning and troubleshooting efforts.
We offer support for the following with versions within the last 12 months:
 Jenkins LTS CloudBees Jenkins Distribution  We offer two levels of support. Check out our terms and conditions for all of the details.
 Gold: Business hours support in the timezone you designate.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Preparation for success</title>
      <link>https://example.com/support/preparationforsuccess/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Oct 2017 15:26:15 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://example.com/support/preparationforsuccess/</guid>
      <description>There is some preparation needed on the customer’s part
Your Jenkins team Jenkins is usually managed, configured and used by team members with different roles. Here is an example of different roles and responsibilities which can be adjusted to your organization:
   Role Responsabilities and Duties     Project Business Sponsor This is more of a strategic role, overseeing how Jenkins is useful in impacting the business.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>